Steel has existed for thousands of years.
钢铁存在了数千年。
But it wasn't until the 19th century that it became an essential commodity.
但直到19世纪，它才成为必需品。
The invention of the Bessemer process revolutionized the steel industry, spurring the growth of major cities and giving birth to the industrial revolution.
贝塞默法的发明彻底改变了钢铁工业，推动了主要城市的增长，并催生了工业革命。
From the construction of towering skyscrapers to the manufacturing of autos and household appliances, steel remains a backbone of civilization.
从高耸入云的摩天大楼的建造到汽车和家电的制造，钢铁仍是文明的支柱。
But the emergence of the modern steel industry has also contributed to the beginning of what would become today's climate concerns.
但现代钢铁工业的出现也导致了今天的气候问题的开端。
So the steel industry globally accounts for about 7 to 9% of CO2 emissions. And so there really is this big need to decarbonize.
全球钢铁工业约占二氧化碳排放的7至9％。因此，迫切需要脱碳。
About 70% of today's steel is produced using the blast furnace method, which relies heavily on coal to generate the heat necessary to reduce iron ore resulting in large amounts of carbon emissions.
今天约70％的钢铁是使用高炉法生产的，该方法严重依赖煤炭产生所需的热量，从而产生大量的碳排放。
Every tonne of crude steel produced using this technique emits around two tonnes of CO2. So Green Steel promises to change this whole dynamic.
使用这种方法生产的每吨原钢会排放约两吨二氧化碳。因此，绿色钢铁承诺改变这一现状。
Also known as sustainable steel or fossil free steel. Green Steel is a revolutionary concept that aims to transform the industry by replacing coal with clean energy products in the production process.
绿色钢铁，又称可持续钢铁或无化石燃料钢铁，是一种革命性的概念，旨在通过将煤炭替换为清洁能源产品来转变工业。
Green hydrogen as a substitute to coal in the production process. So to make it simple, well, really replacing coal by wind and solar.
在生产过程中使用绿色氢气代替煤炭。简而言之，就是用风能和太阳能取代煤炭。
Substituting carbon heavy material with water vapor would bring net steel emissions to essentially zero and create a ripple effect that could reconfigure the structure of the industry and create opportunities for new entrants to be disruptive by making technologies and services more accessible and affordable. But major headwinds remain.
用水蒸汽代替碳重材料将使净钢排放量几乎降至零，并产生连锁效应，重新配置产业结构，为新进入者提供更易获取和负担得起的技术和服务。但也存在巨大的挑战。
So when we look at the amount of renewable energy that's needed for the steel industry to move towards green steel, we do not have enough clean energy today.
要使钢铁工业转向绿色钢铁，需要大量的可再生能源。目前尚不足够。
The technology required to decarbonize still exists, but significant infrastructure changes are required to support and scale low cost green electricity. Construction of green hydrogen production tools. Iron Reduction facilities and electric arc furnaces are just a few of the necessary investments.
脱碳所需的技术已经存在，但需要进行重大的基础设施改变，以支持和扩大低成本的绿色电力。绿色氢气生产设施、铁还原设施和电弧炉的建设只是必要投资的一部分。
But it isn't going to be cheap. You're going to need a huge amount of capital investment. And in Europe alone, for example, all analysts think that it could cost around $130 billion.
但这并不便宜。需要巨额资本投入。仅在欧洲，估计需要约1300亿美元。
Numbers that size, obviously beg the question who will cover the costs? Initiatives are already in place to incentivize the transition and subsidize the upfront investment. One such measure, the United States Inflation Reduction Act, or I.R.A., aims to drive down the cost of key green steel inputs and make the goal of replacing coal with electricity in the production of steel achievable.
这样规模的数字显然会引发问题：谁来承担这些费用？目前已经有措施鼓励过渡并补贴前期投资。其中之一是美国的"联邦通胀减缓法案"，旨在降低关键绿色钢铁原材料的成本，并实现将煤炭替换为电力生产钢铁的目标。
The IRA is a game changer in terms of reducing the cost of clean energy in the United States. This provides a truly massive boost in terms of the economics and the scaling of clean energy.
"联邦通胀减缓法案"在降低美国清洁能源成本方面将起到改变游戏规则的作用。这将在经济和清洁能源的规模扩大方面提供真正巨大的推动。
European policymakers are also sharpening plans to support the transition with funding hydrogen infrastructure investment and carbon border taxes. But further efforts may be needed to make green steel a reality.
欧洲政策制定者也正在加强支持过渡的计划，投资氢气基础设施和碳边界税。但可能需要更多努力才能实现绿色钢铁的目标。
Achieving net zero carbon neutrality and really halting the impact of climate change is dependent on lots of different factors. But steel is a major contributor of greenhouse gases and steel will continue to be a really important materials globally. So finding a way to decarbonize the sector is really crucial if we are to achieve net zero goals.
实现净零碳中立，真正停止气候变化的影响取决于许多不同因素。但钢铁是温室气体的主要排放来源，而且钢铁在全球范围内仍将是非常重要的材料。因此，如果我们要实现净零目标，找到脱碳该行业的方法至关重要。
To read our comprehensive blue paper Green Steel 2.0, which details the industry transformation, potential regional deep dives and other key topics. Click the link below.
阅读我们的全面蓝皮书《绿色钢铁2.0》，详细了解产业转型、潜在的区域深度分析和其他关键话题。点击下方链接。